

Laura Olivia Sutarni Lamanepa

lauralamanepa25@gmail.com

About Me

I am currently in my third semester at Undiksha, studying Information Systems. I have a keen interest in UX design and enjoy discovering innovative approaches to design challenges. I am enthusiastic about understanding user behavior and crafting intuitive, accessible experiences. In addition to my studies, I am always motivated to learn about new technologies and design trends to improve my skills and contribute meaningfully to projects.

Education

2021 - 2024 | SMA Negeri 1 Adonara Timur

2024 - Present | Ganesha University of Education | Information System Study Program

Experience

2022- 2023 | Core Member of Student Council

Joined the student council of Senior High School 1 Adonara Timur, with the position of core secretary for the 2022-2023 period, during the term of office has participated in many activities related to the student council

Achievement

2023 | The winner of the News Reading Competition

The winner of the News Reading Competition at the high school level, held in October 2023,. I was selected for my outstanding performance in reading and presenting news creatively.

2023 | The winner of the Story Telling Competition

Won first place in the Storytelling Competition for an engaging performance, expressive narration, and originality in delivering the story.

Skills

Language: Indonesian, English

Microsoft Office UX/UI Design & Prototyping | Communication & Teamwork